Woman's Building
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Administrative Files, circa 1970-1991, Series 1:; (Box 1-9; 9 linear ft.)
  - Board of Directors, 1974-1991, 1.2:
    - Committees, 1977-1991, 1.2.3:
      - Program Committee Minutes, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Program Committee Minutes, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Program Committee Minutes, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Program Committee, circa 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - Program Committee, circa 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Program Committee, circa 1986 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Program Committee, circa 1987 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Program Committee, circa 1988 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Program Committee, circa 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Public Relations Committee Minutes, 1982-1984, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Summer Executive Committee Minutes, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - Summer Executive Committee Minutes, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - Writing Committee Minutes, 1978, 1984-1991 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Writing Committee, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Writing Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - Writing Committee, Ratings, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Advisory Council, 1979-1989, 1.2.4:
      - Committees and Goals, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Member Biographies and Invitation Letters - A-D, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Member Biographies and Invitation Letters - E-H, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Member Biographies and Invitation Letters - I-L, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Member Biographies and Invitation Letters - M-N, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Member Biographies and Invitation Letters - O-R, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Member Biographies and Invitation Letters - S-W, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Member Biographies and Invitation Letters - A-Z, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Member Biographies and Invitation Letters - A-L, 1986-1989 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Member Biographies and Invitation Letters - M-Y, 1986-1989 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Membership Roster, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Orientation Packet, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Orientation Packet, Draft, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Stern, Lila Wellings, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Publications, 1973-1990, 1.3:
    - Women's Graphic Center Newsletter, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Women's Graphic Center Newsletter, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - The Newsletter of the Woman's Building, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - The Newsletter of the Woman's Building, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - The Newsletter of the Woman's Building, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - The Newsletter of the Woman's Building, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - The Woman's Building Calendar, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - The Woman's Building Calendar, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - The Woman's Building Calendar, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - The Woman's Building Calendar, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - W.B., 1991 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Spinning Off, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Spinning Off, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Spinning Off, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Spinning Off, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Spinning Off, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Womanspace, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Chrysalis, circa 1977-1978, (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 33-34)
    - Chrysalis, circa 1978 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Publicity and Outreach 1973-1990, 1.4:
    - Advertising, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Advertising Campaign, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Advertising in Ms. Magazine, 1976-1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Articles on the Woman's Building by Sheila de Bretteville, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Articles on the Woman's Building by Terry Wolverton, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Classified Ads, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - General Education Brochure, circa 1981 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Grandview Location, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - New York Trip, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1985, January-June (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1985, July-December (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, January-May, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1986, June-August (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, September-December, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1987, January-April (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1987, May-August (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1987, September-December (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1988, January-September (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1988, October-December (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Press Kit, "Incredible Shrinking Woman," 1981 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Press Kit, "The Bell Jar," 1979 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Press Kit, Conference on Women's Culture in American Society, 1880-1980, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Press Releases, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Press Releases, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Press Releases, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Press Releases, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Press Releases, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Press Releases, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Press Releases, 1979, January-May (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Press Releases, 1979, June-December (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Press Releases, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Press Releases, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Press Releases, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Press Releases, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Press Releases, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Press Releases, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Press Releases, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Press Releases, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Press Releases, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Press Releases, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Press Releases, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Press Releases, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, 1978, January-April (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, 1978, May-December (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Printed Event Annoucements, circa 1976-1981, (4 folders) (Box 8, Folder 26-29)
    - Post Cards, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Publicity Costs and Budget, circa 1979 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Spinning Off Production, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - The Stars Guide, circa 1976-1980 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Tours and Lectures, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Woman's Building Brochure, Draft, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Woman's Building Brochure, Draft, circa 1980 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Fundraising and Membership, 1974-1990, 1.5:; (Box 8-9; 1.33 linear ft.)
    - Board Recruitment, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Campaigns to Individuals, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Consultants Group, Fundraising Feasibility Study, 1987, (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 39-41)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Direct Mail Membership Drive, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Donation Inquiries, 1985-1989 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Direct Mail Membership Drive, circa 1979 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Donations, Wine, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Donor Events, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Donor Research, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Donors, Less Than $100, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Donors, More Than $100, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Donors Circle, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Donors Circle, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 52-53)
    - Event, Judy Chicago, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Event, Judy Chicago, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Event, Cooking Demonstration, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Event, PHRANC, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Event, 10K Run, circa 1979-1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Foundation Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Foundation Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Foundations, Ahmanson, Atlantic Richfield, Ford, and Film Fund, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Foundations, Denied Applications, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Foundations, Denied Applications, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Foundations, Expired Contracts, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Foundations, General Application, circa 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Foundations, Liberty Hill, Playboy, and Ms. Foundation, 1976-1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Foundations, Ms. Foundation for Women Proposal, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Foundations, Ms. Foundation for Women Proposal, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Foundations, TOSCO Request, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Fundraising Committee Work, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Fundraising Book, circa 1980 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Fundraising Report, Sara LaRiviere, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Membership Ledger, Women's Graphic Center, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Membership Lists, circa 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Membership, Non-Renewing Letters, circa 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Membership Outreach Project, circa 1980 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Membership Solicitation and Renewal Campaigns, 1982-1987 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Membership Solicitation and Renewal Campaigns, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Membership Solicitation and Renewal Letters, Template, 1978-1988 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Membership Survey, 1987, (7 folders) (Box 9, Folder 24-30)
    - Membership Survey Results, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Past Inquiries to Corporations, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Solicitation, Lily Tomlin and Diane Keaton, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Special Appeals, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Special Appeals, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Vesta Awards, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Vesta Awards Correspondence, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Vesta Awards Correspondence, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Vesta Awards Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Vesta Awards Event Planning, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Vesta Awards Event Planning, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Vesta Awards Event Planning, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Vesta Awards Nominees (A-G), 1985 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Vesta Awards Nominees (H-Y), 1985 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Vesta Awards, Proposal, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Vesta Awards, Voting, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Vesta Awards, Voting, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Vesta Awards, Winners (A-H), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Vesta Awards, Winners (L-W), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Education Programs, 1971-1991, Series 2:; (Box 10-14; 4.9 linear ft.)
  The files within this series document the Woman's Building education programs, including administrative records, curriculum development files, program evaluations, student recruitment and retention, outreach and publicity files. Series also includes individual workshop, conference, and program documentation. The files are arranged alphabetically within each subseries.
  The Education Program files are arranged into five subseries:
  2.1: Administrative Files, 1975-1991
  2.2: Feminist Studio Workshop, 1971-1982
  2.3: Extension Program, 1975-1981
  2.4: Slide Library, 1975-1990
  2.5: Los Angeles Women's Video Center, 1975-1981
  - Administrative Files, 1975-1991, 2.1:
    - Adoption Writing Workshop, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Advertising in Ms. Magazine, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Alvarez, Gloria, Artists-in-Residence Grant, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Artists Survival Skills, Nat Dean, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - "Artists Who are Mothers," 1988 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Bradley, Ann, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Class Demographics, circa 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Class Proposals, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Class Proposals, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Conference, "Women in Design: The Next Decade," 1975 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Conference of Women Performance Artists, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Conference on Women's Culture in American Society, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Conference on Women's Culture in American Society - Funding, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Conference on Women's Culture in American Society, Publicity, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Conference, Women's Culture at Work, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Conference, Women Being Successful as Women in Their Workplaces, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Course Proposals, circa 1990 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Demographic Date, circa 1980, (3 folders) (Box 10, Folder 24-26)
    - Education Committee Meeting Minutes, November 1, 1979 - December 30, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Education Committee Meeting Minutes, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Education Committee Meeting Minutes, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Evaluation Model for Individual Classes, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Feminist Education Graphics Project, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Finger, Anne, Artist-in-Residence Grant, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Forms, circa 1980 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Goddess Lecture Series, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Grant Opportunities, 1985-1988 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Job Description for Education Director, circa 1980 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Lecture, Feminist Theories about Art with Sandra Hale, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Lecture, Jeanne Pool, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Lecture, Mary Daly, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Lesbian Art Project, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Management by Objectives Consultancy, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Manual, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Old Girls 3 Association, circa 1981 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Outreach and Enrollment Plan, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Performance Art Program, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Performance Art Program, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Performance Art Program, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Personnel, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Prado, Holly, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Press Releases, 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Procedures, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Program Evaluation, 1986-1989 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Program Development, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Program Development, 1980-1981, (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 54-55)
    - Programs, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Programs, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Questionnaire Templates, circa 1980 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Salon Series, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Salon Series, Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Scholarship, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Summer Art Program, 1978, (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 62-63)
    - Summer Art Program, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Summer Art Program, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Summer Art Program, Evaluations, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Summer Art Programs, Teacher Applications, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Survey, circa 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Teacher Contracts, circa 1983-1985, (2 folders) (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
    - Teacher Contracts, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Teacher Skills Checklist, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Timelines, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Variations of the Goddess, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Visual Arts Program, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - "The Way We Look, the Way We See: Art Criticism for Women in the '90s" Conference, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - The Way We Look, the Way We See: Proceedings of the 1988 Conference, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 11, Folder 14-15)
    - "West Coast Women's Salon," 1985 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Women's Video Access Course, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Workshop, Collage with Deborah Lawrence, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Workshop, Fetish Making and Effigy Figures with Rosalie Friis-Ross, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Workshop, Journalkeeping with Kay Hagen, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Workshop, "Masking/Unmasking War" with Rosalie Ortega, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Workshop "No Limits" with Betsy Damon, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Workshop, Susan B. Anthony Birthday Celebration and Organizaing Workshop, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Workshop, Unlearning Racism with Ricky Sherover-Marcuse, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Workshop Evaluations, Printmaking with Patty Sue Jones, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Workshop Evaluations, Collage with Deborah Lawrence, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 11, Folder 26-27)
    - Workshop Evaluations, Collage, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Workshops, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Writers Program, 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Writers Workshops, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Feminist Studio Workshop, 1971-1982, 2.2:
    - Administrative Notebook, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Administrative Notebook, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Administrative Notebook, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Articles, circa 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Brochure - Draft, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - California School of Arts, Class Evaluations, 1971, (4 folders) (Box 11, Folder 37-40)
    - Center for Feminist Art Historical Studies, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Class Schedules, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Core Document, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence (includes student letters), 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence (includes student letters), circa 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence (includes student letters), circa 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence with Sheila de Bretteville, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Creative Journal Writing Class, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Curriculum, 1976-1980 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Curriculum, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Degree Information, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Faculty Goals and Skills, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Final Evaluations, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - First Newsletter, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Ground Rules, Signed, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Material for Catalog and Brochure, circa 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - New Moves Scholarship Program, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - New Moves Scholarship Program, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - New Moves Scholarship Program, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - New Moves Scholarship Program, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - New Moves Scholarship Program, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - New Moves Scholarship Program Applications, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - New Moves Scholarship Program Applications, 1982, (3 folders) (Box 12, Folder 8-10)
    - New Moves Scholarship Program, Planning Meeting, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Organizational Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Orientation, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Orientation, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Outreach, circa 1975-1978 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Planning, circa 1977-1980, (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 16-17)
    - Pragmatic Nurturer, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Publicity, 1975-1981 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Recruitmant and Class Schedule, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Recruitment Questionnaire, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Strategies to Meet Budget Deficit, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Recruitment Questionnaire, Completed, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Structure and Program, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Student Correspondence - A-J, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Student Correspondence - L-M, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Student Correspondence - N-R, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Student Correspondence - S-T, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Student Correspondence - U-Z, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Student Exhibit, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Student Writings, circa 1976-1980 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Testimonial Packet, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Tuition, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Unidentified Manuscript, circa 1972-1980, (3 folders) (Box 12, Folder 34-36)
    - Video Class, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Visual Arts Class, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Women's Work, Writings from the Workshop, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Writers' Program, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Writings about the Workshop, circa 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Extension Program, 1975-1981, 2.3:
    - Brochure Drafts, circa 1980 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence with Teachers, 1975-1978 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Course Descriptions, 1978, Fall (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Course Descriptions, 1980, Fall (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Course Descriptions, 1981, Winter, (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 47-48)
    - Course Descriptions, 1981, Spring (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Course Proposals, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Course Proposals, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Course Proposals, 1978, Spring (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Course Proposals, 1978, Summer (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Course Proposals, 1979, Winter (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Course Proposals, 1979, Summer (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Course Proposals, 1979, Fall (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Course Proposals, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Course Proposals, 1981, Winter (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Course Proposals, 1981, Spring (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Course Schedules, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Course Schedules, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Course Syllabus, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Creating the Film Sappho, circa 1980 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Democratic Data for FIPSE Grant, circa 1980 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Faculty, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Flyers and Brochures, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Flyers and Brochures, 1977-1980 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Forms, circa 1980 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Form Letters for Teachers, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 20)